export const present1list = {
  1: {
    question: 'if it is not your own body',
    answer: 'the secret of someone else',
    success: false,
    char: 'C',
    hint: 'is it like being born again?',
  },
  2: {
    question: 'similar to 1,000,000,000, but way cooler',
    answer: 'billio',
    success: false,
    char: '0',
    hint: 'this many boxes',
  },
  3: {
    question: `where'd he go, where'd he go?!`,
    answer: 'bathroom',
    success: false,
    char: 'H',
    hint: 'NOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO',
  },
  4: {
    question: 'something bitches love',
    answer: 'leaves',
    success: false,
    char: 'L',
    hint: `this photo feels like it's missing something... is it... `,
  },
  5: {
    question: 'spider does not have this',
    answer: 'pusspuss',
    success: false,
    char: 'P',
    hint: 'NOOOOOOO',
  },
  6: {
    question: 'i guess not',
    answer: 'i disagree',
    success: false,
    char: '1',
    hint: 'the only applicable response',
  },
  7: {
    question: 'ive got dibs on',
    answer: 'raul',
    success: false,
    char: 'R',
    hint: 'totally PARTYYYYY!!!!',
  },
  8: {
    question: 'this much guacamole is too much guacamole',
    answer: 'gallon',
    success: false,
    char: 'G',
    hint: 'asking for a pal',
  },
  9: {
    question: 'start the halloween season off right with',
    answer: 'spoopy',
    success: false,
    char: 'S',
    hint: 'oct 1st',
  },
  10: {
    question: 'start the christmas season off right with',
    answer: 'shnegg shnogg',
    success: false,
    char: 'S',
    hint: 'was late this year',
  },
  11: {
    question: 'the place that yoj was born',
    answer: 'dunkin donuts',
    success: false,
    char: 'D',
    hint: 'lincroft',
  },
  12: {
    question:
      'character not included in the epic remake of warner bros harry potter and the prisoner of azkaban',
    answer: 'dudley',
    success: false,
    char: 'D',
    hint: 'first half of the movie, first name only',
  },
  13: {
    question:
      'cast this to ward yourself from all manner of nefarious curses, hexes, or jinxes',
    answer: 'protect spell',
    success: false,
    char: 'P',
    hint: '* waves hand in across face *',
  },
  14: {
    question: `never cavemen, sometimes hungry`,
    answer: 'ghosts',
    success: false,
    char: 'G',
    hint: 'also spooky',
  },
  15: {
    question: 'üëÅ üåì  2Ô∏è‚É£  üí©,  üêë  ü¶µd  2Ô∏è‚É£',
    answer: 'leave',
    success: false,
    char: 'L',
    hint: 'i really gotta go, so that means you gotta',
  },
  16: {
    question:
      'if you were a vegetable, according to you, you would be this vegetable',
    answer: 'no',
    success: false,
    char: 'N',
    hint:
      'i told you i would be corn but thats all the real information we got from that convo',
  },
}

export const present2list = {
  1: {
    question:
      '2020 vivian would have been prepared for the lack of toilet paper, but would probably have an unnecessary abundance of',
    answer: 'crackers',
    success: false,
    char: 'C',
    hint: 'you once had an entire shelf dedicated to these',
  },
  2: {
    question: `you're dead to me`,
    answer: `you're dear to me`,
    success: false,
    char: '0',
    hint: 'bitmoji love',
  },
  3: {
    question: `who's winning?`,
    answer: 'jake is winning',
    success: false,
    char: 'J',
    hint: 'i hate you kyle herring; (full phrase)',
  },
  4: {
    question: 'should i paint him in this style?',
    answer: 'gargoyles',
    success: false,
    char: '9',
    hint: `"when you said 'this style' did you just show her a bunch of pictures of ______."`,
  },
  5: {
    question: `siht niw ot puc eht teg`,
    answer: 'draziwirt tnemanruot',
    success: false,
    char: 'T',
    hint: '* flips paper *',
  },
  6: {
    question: 'üá∑üá∫üèò',
    answer: 'duplex',
    success: false,
    char: 'R',
    hint: 'foot muscle',
  },
  7: {
    question: `'boys go to jupiter to get more stupider' 'well... you kind of contradict yourself with that statement...'`,
    answer: 'mine own eyes',
    success: false,
    char: 'M',
    hint: 'these roll into the back of mine own head',
  },
  8: {
    question: 'üñê... üëé',
    answer: 'boo hiss',
    success: false,
    char: 'R',
    hint: 'cheney',
  },
  9: {
    question: 'even worse than bad',
    answer: 'bad with a capital bad',
    success: false,
    char: '8',
    hint: 'like sooo bad',
  },
  10: {
    question: `dholna, vaje tumbe val taar / soode dil de pukar / aaja karle ye pyar`,
    answer: 'tunak tunak tun',
    success: false,
    char: 'T',
    hint: `‡§§‡•Å‡§®‡§ï ‡§§‡•Å‡§®‡§ï ‡§§‡•Ç‡§Å, ‡§§‡•Å‡§®‡§ï ‡§§‡•Å‡§®‡§ï ‡§§‡•Ç‡§Å / ‡§§‡•Å‡§®‡§ï ‡§§‡•Å‡§®‡§ï ‡§§‡•Ç‡§Å, ‡§¶‡§æ ‡§¶‡§æ ‡§¶‡§æ`,
  },
  11: {
    question: 'when you dont get that strike',
    answer: 'chance missed',
    success: false,
    char: 'C',
    hint: '!!!!!!!!!!!!!',
  },
  12: {
    question: `i like dogs`,
    answer: 'buzz buzz',
    success: false,
    char: '8',
    hint: `i'll say this because you can't`,
  },
  13: {
    question: 'holy shit',
    answer: 'banana pants',
    success: false,
    char: '8',
    hint: 'üçåüëñ',
  },
  14: {
    question: 'you in my walls cosplaying as',
    answer: 'kreacher',
    success: false,
    char: 'K',
    hint: 'im giving you a sock so fast',
  },
  15: {
    question: 'you know a weird amount about',
    answer: 'moose',
    success: false,
    char: 'R',
    hint: 'the males go like enngh enngh but females are like eh eh',
  },
  16: {
    question: 'the outrage, the audacity',
    answer: 'how dare',
    success: false,
    char: 'H',
    hint:
      'you think taron edgerton looks like justin beiber you absolute walnut?',
  },
  // C0J9-TRMR-8TC8-8KRH
}
